omniplex.ie 2016-03-26

# Omniplex Cinemas - Book Films Tickets and View Cinema Listings | Privacy

## Privacy Policy

The Omniplex Cinema Group highly values the privacy of our customers. This policy is intended to explain to you how we use any information that you may provide to us when visiting our website.

### Collection of Personal Information

Any information which is provided by you will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality and in accordance with the terms of the Data Protection Acts 1988 to 2003, Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24th October 1995 on the Protection of Individuals with regard to the Processing of Personal Data and on the Free Movement of such data, and any implementing and/or amending legislation as may be adopted in Ireland from time to time.

When purchasing tickets online a customer is asked for the following information:

  * Name
  * Phone Number 
  * Email Address
  * Credit card details

Your email and phone number are collected for the purpose of notification if changes to schedule were to occur or if there was some other problem with your booking.

### Security of Personal and Payment Information

Omniplex Cinema Group maintains the following controls to protect the security of information you provide us, including credit or debit card and address details:

  * Use of secure server using SSL technology to verify credit or debit card details
  * Security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information
  * Use of Cookies & Other Technical Information

When visiting our Omniplex Cinemas website, cookies are only used to keep track of what items you are ordering online. Once you have completed your order and had the order confirmed via your credit or debit card. If you have specified that no cookies be allowed on your pc/laptop then you will not be able to make any online purchases.

Statistical and analytical information collected through the standard operation of our internet server and logs provides us with general and not individually specific information. Omniplex Cinema Group will make no attempt to identify individual users or to associate any technical information collected through the standard operation of our internet server and logs with any individual user.

Omniplex Cinema Group, its directors and staff shall not be liable in respect of any claims, emergencies, demands, causes of action, damages losses, expenses, including without limitation, reasonable legal fees and costs of proceedings arising out of or in connection with the use and/or dissemination of personal information relating to you in accordance with this privacy policy and your consents.

Omniplex Cinema Group website contains links to other web sites. Omniplex Cinema Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy and data collection practices.

### Amendments

Omniplex Cinema Group reserves the right in its sole discretion to amend this privacy statement at any time, and you should regularly check this privacy statement for any amendments.

### Contact us about privacy

We welcome any feedback on any privacy concern that you may have. We will use very effort to comply with this privacy policy and take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. Omniplex Cinema Group shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy policy. Omniplex Cinema Group may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Omniplex Cinema Group or (b) protect and defend the rights and property of Omniplex Cinema Group and its products This privacy policy shall be governed by the laws of the Republic of Ireland.

To Contact us simply send your details on our contact us page
